It's morning...
What a wonderful dream.
No better dream
than a nightmare.
I see it...
I see your pain. as well...
You win. Jugo.
I also see your loyalty...
My son born of darkness.
Come...
No one can stop me.
Their powers switch only
while Yhwach is asleep.
That's right.
Right now. Yhwach does not
have the power of "The Almighty."
He's now in
the upper level of Wahr Welt.
Head up there. Kurosaki!
Ishida!
Are you actually gonna stay here?
If he has Yhwach's powers.
then it's all the more reason—!
Quit talking and go!
Besides. those won't be my last words.
Is everything okay. Inoue?
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
I just...kinda felt relieved.
Relieved?
How do I put it?
I never believed Ishida
actually joined the Quincy. but...
hearing him say it directly
was a relief. I guess.
I was just thinking
Ishida was still the same Ishida...
What's that?!
- Chad!
- Sado!
I'm okay.
Just go!
Okay...
Let's do this.
Turn to sand!
Oh. it's you. Ganju.
Where have you been?
"Where have you been?" my butt!
You left me
and went off on your own!
I got separated and got lost!
That's when I saw this perfect
moment to use my skills.
A group of stone statues
is perfect!
My Seppa was made for this!
Hey. listen to me!
- I'm listening.
- Are you really. though?
Give me a reaction or something!
Do you like doing
unglamorous grunt work. Ganju?
Ichigo only sees the path
that's in front of him.
That's how he is.
Our job is to clean out the castle
and pave a path back for Ichigo.
Haschwalth can't see
the complete future...
You surprise me. Uryu Ishida.
You look completely different
from who you were earlier.
You seem so full of hope now.
I see.
Setting aside whether or not
I am full of hope or not.
the fact that you're surprised...
...means you did not foresee me
being filled with hope. did you?
At that time.
he didn't confirm or deny it.
Like I keep telling you.
I see everything.
In that case. I'll just confirm
how much you can see.
They're not hitting him...!
So. he can see everything.
after all?
Seems you're limiting
my angles of attack
by standing with your back
to the walls and ceiling.
Then you need only to concentrate
on what's in front of you.
I praise you for fighting
a cerebral battle. Uryu Ishida.
As I'd expect from you.
Grand Master.
But I don't appreciate your praise.
Your life is in my hands...
Right now. the power of
His Majesty fills my body.
Trying to take these powers
from me is futile.
Uryu Ishida...
You cannot be me.
I am His Majesty's other half.
I am a Quincy born to be together
with His Majesty.
That is why His Majesty entrusted
his powers to me.
Can you see it?
Can you see what is
about to happen next?
What is that?!
This is His Majesty's true wish.
It's a hit!
Jinta Home-Run!
Uh...
What is that huge crack?!
It's identical to that "distortion"
Kisuke was investigating...
Wait a minute!!
A "distortion" is a concentration
of dangerous energy...
I thought the Manager
and the others fixed it!
He was supposed to. but...
Isn't it dangerous to stay in
this town...or even in this world?
Isn't that right. Tessai?
Mr. Urahara...
Did you say. his true wish?
Everything is proceeding according
to His Majesty's plan
that began with the attack
on Soul Society.
The extermination of
massive numbers of Hollows
from the World of the Living
greatly upset the balance of souls
Our invasion fooled
many Soul Reapers.
The deaths of Genryusai Yamamoto
followed by members of Squad Zero
upset the balance
in this world to its core.
And the Soul King. who was
the linchpin of the Three Worlds.
became a part of
His Majesty's power.
This crack is a prelude
to the annihilation
of the Three Worlds.
Annihilation of the Three Worlds...
What are you trying to do?
You've probably
heard before.
It's called "Welt."
We are creating a new world.
We will destroy the Three Worlds
to create a monarchy
of and for Quincy.
That is His Majesty's true wish
and it is the duty Stern Ritter
must fulfill for their brethren.
You are not a part of that future
that I see.
Dealing with traitors...
...is also my job!
Spoken like
His Majesty's mouthpiece.
After hearing what you said.
my to-do list just grew.
First. defeat you to eliminate
"The Almighty."
Second. eliminate this rift
and protect the Three Worlds.
Can't believe
I didn't have to move...
...to survive all that!
I feel it. I feel myself moving
farther away from death.
If my immunity is the ultimate way
to avoid death.
maybe I have immunity to
thank for this as well.
What do you think.
Yoruichi Shihoin?
Sorry. I thought you were talking
to yourself. so I wasn't listening.
More like you
couldn't listen. right?
I fired off a hybrid Gift Ball
of Spiritual Pressure.
Oxygen. and Nitrogen.
You didn't have the luxury of
listening to pointless mutterings...
Honestly. I'm surprised
you're not dead in your condition.
Likewise...
After all that fiddling
with fatal dosage...
I'm not sure why you adjusted it
enough to keep me barely alive.
You're wrong.
I did the best that I could.
Anyone else would have
been dead by now.
Stop ignoring that you're a freak
and making it sound like
I went easy on you.
It's a real bummer.
Yushiro won't last much longer...
But I don't have the strength
to heal him in my condition.
In that case!
Don't bother.
I don't know what you're up to...
But you're at death's door.
You couldn't even react
at this distance.
No matter what you try
in the state you're in now.
I'm confident I can strike first.
That's pretty fatal.
don't you think. Yoruichi Shihoin?
Indeed!
You've been dealt
a fatal wedgie. Yoruichi.
That hurt my chin!
I came all this way to save you.
Why'd you kick me?!
What made you think I wouldn't?!
Look at me!
Stop staring at my butt!
Sorry...
You're right. Perhaps ‘wedgie"
was a bit vulgar.
That's not why I kicked you!
And stop touching my butt
while apologizing!
Kisuke Urahara...
Another troublemaker
to deal with...
Oh. you know me?
Much obliged.
Do I know you?
You may not know this.
but you're one
of the Special Threats
designated personally
by His Majesty.
I'm honored to be included
among such esteemed company.
It's a privilege. but he's
giving me too much credit.
Isn't that right. Yoruichi?
What?!
What did he do?
How is Yoruichi Shihoin
able to move?!
Did he undo my Death Dealing?!
How?!
No. this is exactly
what I've been told about.
The five Special Threats
were chosen
for their incalculable aspects.
Ichigo Kurosaki
for his "potential."
Kenpachi Zaraki
for his "combat strength."
Ichibei Hyosube for his "wisdom."
Sosuke Aizen
for his "Spiritual Pressure."
And Kisuke Urahara
for his "incalculable tricks!"
Regardless of what strategy
you use.
he will always outsmart you.
He is the consummate schemer!
Man...Why am I the one
who always has to face
these troublemakers?!
What did you inject into my butt?
It's a secret.
An immunity enhancing
agent you cooked up
while hiding
and eavesdropping on us...
Am I right?
As expected. Yoruichi!
How astute of you.
I had to rush and improvise.
so its effect won't last long.
How long?
About 5 minutes. maybe?
That's plenty!
Shunko!
- Raijin Senkei...
- Hold on. Yoruichi.
What?!
You got more to say?!
Let's try that thing...
No!
Why'd you shoot me down so quick?
Let me try to explain and
negotiate with you...
I never want to be that half-assed.
grotesque form ever again!
I see...
Too bad.
I don't want to do this.
but you force my hand...
Oops! Bummer.
I missed.
Hey...
It's nice that you're able to move.
and it's great
you're excited. but...
I hit you with the Gift Ball when
you were in perfect condition...
Do you really think you can beat me
just because you
recovered a little bit?
Yoruichi!
What just happened?!
W-What kind of form is that?!
Hey. don't ignore me!
Shunko: Raiju Senkei
Shunryu Kokubyo Senki.
That's what.
Okay. but why are you
the one saying it?
Could it be?
Can she not understand
what I'm saying right now?
No way!
How is this happening?
I should be immune to
her Spiritual Pressure already!
It's not possible for
a Soul Reaper's Spiritual Pressure
to change midway like this!
What's going on?!
She's moody.
You know how they say
cats can be fickle?
Yoruichi's moods
in her Kokubyo Senki form
shows in her Spiritual Pressure.
See how she's not coming
after you right now?
It's because she's not in the mood.
Yoruichi's moody to begin with.
but in that form.
her Spiritual Pressure becomes
more erratic.
It's almost like
someone else's Spiritual Pressure.
You know how the flu
spreads every year?
Even if it's not a new strain.
just a tiny mutation
in antigenicity
and last year's strain Type A
spreads again.
It's sort of like that.
Even if your body keeps
building up immunity.
one small change
makes it all for nothing.
Sure. your immunity
acquisition rate
is incredibly fast...
When you're attacked.
you reflexively analyze
the Spiritual Pressure
and build immunity
at a terrifying speed.
It takes you just a minute
to nullify any attack.
But that's not fast enough.
The Spiritual Pressure when
Yoruichi's in Kokubyo Senki
changes 48 times per second.
Hey!
Yoruichi...
I have Yoru-nip for you.
Come here.
Ouch!
Okay. okay!
Oh boy...
I'm the only one
who can control her.
and she can only revert back
if she's in the mood...
I guess that's the drawback
with this form.
Well. Yoruichi in this form is cute
in her own way.
so I don't really mind.
Oh. it's been almost five minutes.
The immuno enhancer
is about to wear off.
You did well. Yoruichi.
Take your time detoxing
from the poison.
I'm going to look for his body
and make sure he's dead.
What's the hell is this?
A Gift Ball Deluxe.
The largest Gift Ball I can create.
Oh! That's not
what's bothering you?
Are you bothered
by the way I look?
It's called Hass Hein.
Not that cool of a name. right?
What are you doing. Orihime?
Yeah...
I was just thinking that
this flower kind of reminds me
of Kurosaki.
What? It does?
Ichigo's not as red
like that flower.
but isn't he
more like that one?
Huh. I think you're right.
Well. it doesn't really matter
which one he is.
We can talk about Ichigo later.
Anyway. let's get going.
We need to finish seeing everything
by half past the hour.
Oh yes. you're right...
Yup. I am!
Double period classes
are such a pain!
Kurosaki's heart must surely be...
...the same color as that flower.
Warm. kind and shining its light
brightly on everything around it....
In order to protect everyone.
That's why I decided...
Kurosaki. I—!
Spiritual Pressure that changes
48 times per second...
Put another way...
I can get a taste of
all 48 versions in one second.
In other words.
if I can withstand her attack
for just one second in
my Vollständig form.
I'll be infected 48 times.
Then all I need...is time to analyze
and acquire immunity.
Oh. and...
Maybe there's a way to alter
her Spiritual Pressure even more.
but it won't do any good.
Just so you don't waste
any time and effort.
out of kindness...
I'll tell you the capabilities
of my Vollständig.
My Vollständig. Hass Hein adapts
to the changes in a poison.
No matter how much the surface
layer of a poison changes.
if the base is the same.
Hass Hein can alter the immunity
and instantly nullify it.
Was that was too wordy?
But you get it. right?
From here on out.
the both of you can change your
Spiritual Pressures all you want.
But you won't be able to put
a scratch on me.
So. what will you do.
Kisuke Urahara?
Don't tell me...
Just because I negated
all your moves from 1 to 10.
that you're at your wit's end!
Don't be so surprised.
I'm just making sure.
I divided the Bereich.
I'm not fond of speaking
in absolutes. you see.
People who do. appear unsure
of themselves. don't they?
I want to be a man
who is in control.
But I will say this.
It is absolutely impossible
to escape this Gift Bereich.
You really don't want us to escape.
do you?
Of course not.
Why even ask?
You and I are enemies.
Well. I hate to be
the one to say this.
but you didn't seem to me like
a guy who acts out of loyalty.
Now that was rude.
I like to think I have twice
the loyalty of a Pomeranian.
But you're not wrong...
Loyalty isn't everything.
I'm interested in His Majesty.
When I say "interested."
does that sound condescending?
Of course.
I don't mean it that way.
The World of the Living.
Hueco Mundo. Soul Society...
Destroying three entire worlds...
...then aiming to build something new!
Who else but His Majesty
could do that?
Let's say.
if we lose His Majesty here...
do you think anybody else like him
would emerge to take his place?
Kisuke Urahara...
You're a smart guy...
You look like a man who has seen
everything there is to see.
Aren't you even a bit curious?
What will His Majesty create after
he destroys the Three Worlds?
Don't you want to see
what it will be?
You're still able to
move that quickly?
That's impressive
inside this Gift Bereich.
No. I don't think I do.
Is that your answer
to my earlier question?
That's too bad.
I thought you'd be more like me.
Perhaps Captain Kurotsuchi
might have said
he wanted to see something new.
Mayuri Kurotsuchi. huh...?
But even in his case.
it doesn't mean he'd want to see
what Yhwach creates.
If you want to see something created
that nobody's ever seen before.
it should be made
by your own hand.
That's how scientists are.
I see.
I don't hate that answer.
Still. I'd rather see
His Majesty's version!
Gift Ring!
It disappeared?!
I use Gift Ring on guys
who are ridiculously strong
on whom the Death Dealing
doesn't work.
It's effect...
focuses the ability of
the Death Dealing on a single point
that's been pierced with
pinpoint accuracy
and instantly killing
that precise section.
It's your fault
for being too strong.
Lowering the lethal dose
did no good.
Eliminating all your moves
didn't do it.
So. destroying
every single organ of yours
is the only way left to kill you.
You've got me here...
You're really hellbent
on killing me!
Guess I have no choice.
Bankai.
Kannon-Biraki Benihime Aratame.
Whoa...
What is that?
That's a Bankai?
Your Bankai...
wasn't in the information
I received from His Majesty.
This is the first time I've used it
among present company.
I see...that's how it is.
So. I might as well ask...
What does it do?
You're actually asking?
I'm not telling.
Well. okay. I figured.
It's just kinda scary confronting it
without knowing what it does.
I get it.
But you'll find out soon enough.
What the...hell is this?!
You're so calm!
Most people are so surprised
that they try to cut off their arm.
As you've now realized.
my Bankai's effect is "ranged."
I don't have the guts
to cut my arm off.
You might have realized
from the first strike...
What...
What is he doing?
Kannon-Biraki Benihime
Aratame's ability...
is reconstructing
whatever it touches.
What?! You can see?!
But I killed your eyes instantly!
I can see!
They've been reconstructed.
you see...
Ugh. I hate this.
I really. really. really
really hate this!
This has turned into
a clash of brute force.
the kind of fight I hate!
I finally dragged you onto my turf
to fight on my terms.
then you go and mess it all up.
You're a bad man. Kisuke Urahara.
But.
you're not perfect!
You haven't forgotten. have you?
My Gift Ball Deluxe is
an inescapable fortress of poison!
You're able to breathe inside of it
only because I'm moderating it!
Give me a break. here!
You're not going to raise
the concentration
of Gift Ball Deluxe even more.
are you?!
As it is.
I can just barely crawl...
That's rich coming from you.
I already know!
Your Bankai is dangerous even
if you're crawling on the ground!
Impressive.
You're quite perceptive.
But it's already too late.
What happened?
It's been bugging me...
You said that this Gift Ball Deluxe
was inescapable.
but you did not say
it was impenetrable.
So. I thought as a test...
Why not create a direct path
into the ball from the outside?
Thank you for your help...
Mr. Grimmjow.
So. you're...
moving around again.
Impressive.
I underestimated you.
What? You're still alive even with
a crushed heart?
I healed him.
On my way here.
The Arrancars who had their masks
torn off by Aizen
can completely transform
their Spiritual Pressures
from an Arrancar's to
a Hollow's using Resurrección.
I thought that might be
useful in battle.
You saw that far ahead?
No.
I told you...
I thought it might come in handy
during battle.
So. I prepared for it.
Take a thousand precautions and
if even one is successful...perfect.
Prepare for
every single possibility.
That's how I am.
That's insane.
How so?
This is a battle.
You lose. you die.
Preparing yourself to death.
to avoid death...
It's something we all do.
don't you think?
You have a point.
I think I finally...
understand why...
you're so frightening...
Stubborn bastard.
Die already.
Mr. Grimmjow!
Killing your enemy was the extent
of our agreement.
Our contract's done.
What the...hell is this?
Oh. I forgot to tell you something...
Bastard! You're still...
When I die.
the effect of Gift Ball Deluxe
intensifies!
It's because the lock that
I unconsciously kept on it
out of fear. to protect myself
is removed.
I would pay my respects to you...
But there's nothing
I can do about it.
I'm guessing you two don't have
the energy left to run.
Sorry about that...
That being said...
Knowing you.
I'm sure you've got an
answer for this. right?
Damn it.
It pisses me off so much.
So. I won't say...
it's fatal...
Damn it!
I'm not letting this thing kill me!
Amazing...
One of the Five Possibilities
he mentioned really happened...
I think there are four
Spiritual Pressures inside.
It will take two round trips.
Where's the entrance?
There?!
It's tiny!
I was actually hoping
to go with Ichigo. but...
Is this it for me?
I'm sorry to leave the rest
up to you like this...
Mr. Kurosaki... Miss Kuchiki...
Everyone...
Do you feel that. Inoue?
Yes.
It's behind that door.
We'll go in two on one.
It may be kinda unfair...
I'll leave you
in charge of defense.
I'm counting on you. Inoue.
Okay!
It's finally happening.
Finally...
I can finally fight
to protect Kurosaki!
Good of you to come.
I've been waiting.
My son of darkness.
Aren't you going to
draw your sword?
That leaves you quite vulnerable...
...is what I want to say. but...
you're not exactly vulnerable.
are you?
It's like I can almost see
your overflowing Spiritual Pressure
take form.
You've grown strong.
No. I should say...
That is the power
you're supposed to have.
Now come!
Will you come from the right?
Or from the left?
I'm waiting in anticipation.
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to strike at me?
I want to enjoy this long-awaited
talk between father and child.
You're...
not my father.
Ah. you speak of Isshin Kurosaki?
He was just a
stand-in father.
I'm sure you've already been told...
of the origin of your power.
I have.
So what?
You're not my father!
You're the man
who killed one of my parents!
Your mother?
Don't be pathetic!
Getsugatensho!
Simply being able to
"see" the future
doesn't mean he can "win."
I simply have to attack
in a way he can't defend
even if he knows it's coming.
I'm going to send you
and that "almighty" power to the grave.
I will rectify your ignorance.
Uryu Ishida.
Simply grasping everything
about a battlefield
is a far cry from "seeing"
how a battle unfolds.
You sent Ichigo Kurosaki to fight
the most important battle.
You probably calculated on Ichigo
defeating His Majesty
when he is without The Almighty.
That was a reasonable strategy.
But a mistaken one.
The power of the Soul King!
What is there to be sad about?
She died as she was supposed to.
She gave birth to you
and lived for me.
What more could she want?
There is no greater happiness!
Kurosaki!
Our conversation is finished.
It was fun.
Now...
Shall we fight. Ichigo?
It was a smart choice to focus on
the The Almighty.
However...
It was overly arrogant of you
to try to measure His Majesty.
The Almighty.
What was it that you thought you knew
about me. Uryu Ishida?
Despair begins now.
Wait. Kurosaki!
A reckless charge.
What did you bring that woman for?
Did hatred make you
lose control of yourself?
Don't be so impatient.
You will eventually be consumed
by me and die.
but it's no fun
if you rush to your death.
Do you have any idea
how much time and
how many miracles it took
to create you?
Don't be impatient.
Don't treat your life so lightly.
Your body...
Your power...
They do not belong to you. Ichigo.
Expend all of your power
and die. Ichigo!
Where am I?
I can't see a thing...
What is this place?
Expend all of your power
and die. Ichigo!
Santenkesshun!
Shitenkoshun!!
Ah. the power of rejection.
I...
reject!
You can't reject me completely.
The same powers that flow
within Ichigo flow within me.
So. you unconsciously
accept my attacks.
Woman...
Consider it an honor...
that a mere human like you.
who overstepped her bounds.
could even be here.
I won't let you...
...hurt him
I will protect him!
And that...
is why...
I reject!
Getsugatensho!
I will kill you.
Such hubris. Ichigo.
To do that would be the same as
killing the world.
For I've already become
the world itself!
While I possess
His Majesty's powers.
I can wield them as I please.
This is the power that I hold
as his other half.
Uryu Ishida. if you did indeed
survive His Majesty's Auswählen.
then prove it once more
by surviving my powers.
Your fight has been a contradiction
from the very beginning.
You should have seen that already.
You know just how fragile
the balance of this world is
and how easily it can be shaken...
Killing His Majesty.
who has become one with the Soul King.
would condemn
this world to its end.
How pathetic.
If we defeat Yhwach.
the world will crumble...
I'm completely aware of that.
Then why...?
But...
Kurosaki might say this...
I'm still going to take you down.
I know the people who have
always protected this world.
You are trampling on the very thing
they want to protect.
There are countless lives
I want to protect.
I want to protect their feelings
and all that they hold dear.
If that means destroying the world.
then so be it...
Here I come.
Getsuga Jujisho!
Have you realized it yet?
Even if you people can win
against His Majesty.
now that the Soul King is gone.
do you realize what will be
necessary to preserve
the world as you know it?
Even that didn't work...
Ichigo...
My son born in the darkness...
You might be ignorant.
but you understand everything
instinctually.
And because
you understand everything.
you hesitate to take me down.
Ichibe Hyosube...
Everything is happening exactly
according to his plan.
He took you in. Ichigo Kurosaki...
and gave you the Soul King's memories
and explained everything.
He did it to judge
whether Ichigo Kurosaki
was worthy of existence.
You are a miracle.
You are human. Soul Reaper.
Hollow. Fullbringer. and Quincy.
You likely never thought about
the true essence of your powers...
Why do you clad yourself
in black?
Black is the color of chaos...
Chaos is the power of
the Soul King.
Black—the color without color—
is nothing less than
the Soul King's Spiritual Pressure.
And the one who controls that black
is Ichibe Hyosube.
I'm sure he said to you.
"Protect the Soul King."
I'm sorry...
So sorry...
You're the only one being taken
for a different reason.
Are you a vessel
capable of withstanding
the power that fills it.
or are you a bowl that shatters?
I was able to receive a tiny bit of
your power to restore my own body.
Please protect the Soul King.
Ichigo!
I will tell you his true intent.
Ichibe Hyosube intended to
install you as the next Soul King.
No way!
He was going to
make you a figurehead
whose only purpose is
to preserve the Three Worlds.
So a world with Soul Reapers as the
pinnacle would be maintained.
That is Ichibe Hyosube's
vision of "peace."
For you. it may as well be "death."
So what?
What?
It's just...
I figured that's what
Kurosaki would say.
Why does it matter if
I become the Soul King or not?!
What I know right now. is...
Unless I take you down.
I'll have nothing to protect!
Yhwach!
What the hell is that monster?
He's so strong. he made you
pee your pants a little. Hachi!
I haven't peed my pants.
Too easy!
Is this all you Thirteen Court
Guard Squad captains can muster
against my Miracle?
I can already barely sense
your faint Spiritual Pressure.
It'll be like stepping on ants
in the sand.
It's close to impossible...
That is exactly why I can find you!
Did you think I wouldn't be able to
find you because it's impossible?
It's a "Miracle" because
the impossible becomes possible!
We weren't listening
to you earlier.
so your "Miracle" is just
gibberish to us. baldy!
I am not bald!
What kinda comeback was that?!
Are you being serious?!
You think I'd fall for that?!
Nah. I didn't.
Not if it was just me.
Sakanade.
The world flipped!
Everything's upside-down.
Now. everybody!
I'll let you hear the Tritone
Tekken Tachikaze!
Super Mashiro Kick!
Chocolate Bar Slider!
Hifuki no Kozuchi!
Nijuichijo Tonbokudari!
It's over.
We did it...
Boy. oh boy...
It'll never end at this rate.
Oh. I know...
I'll just drop this entire area
along with them all.
I can't allow you to let them fall.
Stay frozen here forever.
Who said that?
Captain of Squad 10 of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
Is that so?
I am Stern Ritter Gerard Valkyrie
of the Royal Guards.
Let's be friends!
Sorry.
I didn't come here to be friends.
Bankai.
Daiguren Hyorinmaru.
Shiro...
I see...
What a childish answer...
Kurosaki!
So it falls on the father
to correct the child's error.
I suppose.
He's so fast...
I can't follow
Kurosaki's movements...!
Kurosaki. wait!
Calm down for a second!
I don't understand...
Why rush to your death?
Are you reluctant to show me
all of your power?
Are you afraid I'll take it.
if you show it to me?
But is that all right. Ichigo?
If you die here.
both the World of the Living and
Soul Society are done.
I will end them.
Are you okay with that. Ichigo?
Look.
Your friend is saying
that must not happen.
She's telling you to heal
your wounds and fight.
You never had a choice
to begin with.
Answer. Ichigo!
To the voices of the powerless.
For the weak...
who. without you...
can barely breathe.
Stand up.
Fight.
And die!
Thanks. Inoue.
Sure!
I barely grabbed your clothes...
but you stopped. Kurosaki.
When you looked back.
I didn't see the face of a person
who had lost himself.
I knew you had something in mind.
Yeah...
There was a guy I wanted to wake up
by pumping in some
Quincy Spiritual Pressure.
His sword...
is turning white...
I see...
So that's what
you were trying to do.
Okay. now for the finishing move.
It couldn't even stop him
for a moment...
He's a tough bastard.
Did you think you could stop me
with these ice tricks?
That saved me...
I don't like The Miracle.
but it's powerful.
Agreed.
He's a difficult opponent
to take on one-on-one.
Let me help.
Understood.
Given the difference in height.
two against one
wouldn't be cowardly...
Why are you looking at me
like that?
You wanna say that I'm always
at a height disadvantage?
No. of course not...
That's...not my intent.
- Sorry.
- Then why'd you apologize?!
You hesitated.
and then apologized anyway!
Look at me!
What's this?
Captain classes
all got obliterated together?
So pathetic!
- Here comes trouble...
My...my right hand!
Is stronger!
What's that?
What just happened?!
That's his power.
Any injured area on his body
grows bigger and stronger.
I see.
That means he wasn't this big
from the start.
What?
If you've got something to say.
just say it!
I don't.
You're being hyper-sensitive.
How fun!
Let's find out what happens if
we dice him up into pieces!
That idiot!
What do you think you're doing?
You woulda been sliced in two
if I hadn't held back!
You're more considerate
than I thought.
Now put a little more thought
into it...
Huh? What are you talking about?
What will happen if we make him
any bigger. and he falls?
Nothing.
I'll fall with him and slice him up
on the way down.
If someone with all that mass
falls from this height.
Seireitei will be destroyed!
Stop with the quibbling!
So in other words.
I just have to stop toying with him
and go straight to cracking
his head open. right?
Zaraki!
You made me fall over.
You're strong...
I hate to be cruel.
but you leave me no choice.
A powerful embodiment of darkness
such as yourself
shall become rust on my Hoffnung.
Can't believe I couldn't cut you.
A tough shield
and a tough body. huh?
Makes me wanna cut you even more.
Drink...
Nozarashi.
What is that?
His Shikai?
When did Zaraki...?
So. his sword wasn't
a constant-release type.
No...
Perhaps a constant-release type
never existed in the first place...
You fool!
You chipped my Hoffnung!
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Hyoryusenbi...
Zekku!
Do you wish that badly for despair?
What's this?
What's happening?
What's puzzling you?
My power is The Miracle.
The Miracle turns
the people's wishes into reality.
My indestructible body is enlarged
by the people's fears.
Hoffnung is forged from
the hopes of the people.
When it shatters.
there will be despair!!
I am Gerard Valkyrie!
I am a miracle.
and miracles are what I am.